Zed Poirier

http://zedpoirier.com Zed.Poirier@gmail.com Kitchener, Ontario, Canada

SUMMARY

My skillset focuses on creating immersive experiences by leveraging iterative design principles, stylized 3D modelling, and efficient scripting techniques for quick prototyping.

• VR & Mobile Development

Technical Art Focus

• Rapid Gameplay Prototyping

• Bilingual (English & French)

SKILLS

Languages & Engines: Unity, Godot, C#, C++, HLSL, GLSL, OpenGL 3D Art Software: Blender, Maya, 3DS MAX, Substance Painter

Multimedia: Adobe Suite, OBS, Google Docs

Production: Jira, Trello, GitHub, SVN, Google Drive

EXPERIENCE

Technical Artist - June 2020 to Present **BattleGoat Studios -** Ancaster, ON

- Engineered explosive visual effects using particle systems and shader functions
- Visual development of celestial bodies for a galactic expansion of an RTS franchise
- Researched workflow pipelines for integration of art assets into a custom game engine

3D Digital Artist - April 2019 to April 2020

VARLab - Kitchener, ON

- Developed and integrated digital assets for virtual reality training simulations
- Researched techniques to improve efficiency of asset creation and game performance

Game Master - August 2018 to January 2019

MirageVR - Kitchener, ON

- Documented system bugs and potential performance improvements to the dev team
- Troubleshot technical errors during setup and mid-game to ensure a smooth experience

EDUCATION

- CS50x Certificate, 2020, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA
- Game Design Diploma, 2020, Conestoga College, Kitchener, ON
- Broadcast Television Diploma, 2014, Conestoga College, Kitchener, ON

OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

- I have experience with a variety of skills in computers, model-making, and writing
- Game Master experience in role playing games such as D&D, Blades in the Dark, etc